<resources>
    <string name="classical_music_and_dance_club"><u>Classical Music and Dance Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_classical_music_and_dance_club">Have got an interest in Indian classical traditions in the field of music then MNIT has the perfect rhythms for it too. Join us in the Renaissance of Indian classical music. Be it the beats of Tabla, or the tones of harmonium or the movements of various Classical Dance forms. Explore yourself and find a new meaning of traditions at MNIT JAIPUR. The club seeks to conduct events to promote Indian Classical Dance and Music, Singing and Instrumentals. Spic Macay events will be organised by this club.</string>
    <string name="creative_arts"><u>Creative Arts Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_creative_arts">“The object of art is not to reproduce reality, but to create a reality of the same intensity.”- Alberto Giacometti Art is not a new form of expressing emotions for mankind as it is related to our race from the very beginning of the human race and cultures. The objective of this club is to instigate and instil passion for the arts and culture among the students and faculty. A club dedicated entirely to the field of arts in both traditional and digital forms. It plans to organize events to promote various forms of fine arts, like freehand, sketching, putting up exhibitions of student artists, organizing workshops and competitions.</string>
    <string name="dance"><u>Dance Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_dance">Dance is about the feeling to enjoy a good time with yourself and to jazz on the beats. The Dance Club of MNIT JAIPUR has got a proud history of catching the eyes of spectators at competitions of National level. From Jazz to contemporary, you can explore different variations of dances at dance club. Organize events to promote various forms of Dance among students excluding Indian classical.</string>
    <string name="debating"><u>Debating Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_debating">“Knowing what to say is sense, when to say it is intelligence, how to say it is wisdom, why and how to say it is enlightenment.” To ensure truth and transparency about any theme, it is necessary to confer about it with logical arguments. The club is dedicated to empowering students with confidence and to gain broad, multi-faceted knowledge across several disciplines. The club plans to conduct discussions, extempore, debates to develop oracy skills and critical thinking of students.</string>
    <string name="drama"><u>Drama Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_drama">Drama is the way to express how you feel to others, it will give you the freedom to find the real you. The Dramatics Club encourages students love for language and enhance their literary skills and to display their intellectual and independent thinking skills and imbibe a sense of confidence. Dramatics Society is another enlivening club at MNIT Jaipur that witnesses overwhelming participation. The club conducts various forms of drama events in English and in Hindi. It offers a plethora of opportunities for students interested in acting, directing, stage managing, writing, and designing or building sets, lights, sound, and costumes.</string>
    <string name="english_language"><u>English Language Activities Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_english_language">The world perspective at the hand of young minds. The club presents you an opportunity to showcase your creativity through book reviews, Model United Nations conferences, storytelling, creative writing and all the aspects of English literature. You can rediscover your literary skills and enhance your personality with the help of your fellow mates. Come, Express yourself with other like-minded souls.</string>
    <string name="english_press"><u>English Press Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_english_press">Manage the Institute’s official newsletter at English Press Club. With the Students running Newsletter,Newspaper, Blog that covers College Events, College news, fests, recorded radio notes etc. So much events at your disposal to be an integral part of. Conduct various events like report writing competition editorial writing etc. Learn essential skills which will help you through your journey of life. Come join us at English Press Club and visit the world like Never before.</string>
    <string name="film_making"><u>Film Making Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_film_making">Film making provides a different dimension of visualisation of the surroundings and an art to compile them in a single frame. Films are ways to demolish any stereotypes and to encourage a sense of unity across age ranges, social classes and ethnicities. With a broad vision, MNIT is going to instigate Film Making Club. The main objective of the club is to teach about the principles and stages of film making, cover fests and primary events, animations, sponsor videos and most importantly the after movies, which help us to relive the moments.</string>
    <string name="hindi_language"><u>Hindi Language Activities Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_hindi_language">Planning events that focus on the origins and development of the Hindi language up to the current day falls under the purview of the Hindi Language Activities Club, which oversees organising Hindi literature festivals, book reviews, and other related activities.</string>
    <string name="hindi_press"><u>Hindi Press Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_hindi_press">Hindi newsletter, newspaper, and blog run by students that covers college events, college news, and fests, in addition to recorded radio notes and other issues. Conduct a variety of diverse events, including contests for writing reports and editorials, among other things.</string>
    <string name="music"><u>Music Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_music">The Music Club encourages and provides a platform for the students to participate in a wide range of musical activities, such as singing and playing instruments; however, Indian classical music is not included in this category.</string>
    <string name="photography"><u>Photography Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_photography">Photographs are not just a picture it is an emotion which can weave a whole story about an event. It develops the critical thinking of students and provide them vision to explore the world differently which normal people can\'t imagine about. The club encourages students to take part in a variety of events and activities that are related to photography, such as competitions and exhibitions, and use their photography skills to record the many and different activities that take place at the college.</string>
    <string name="poetry"><u>Poetry Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_poetry">Give students a platform to develop and hone their poetic skills through engagement with a wide range of events. These activities can range from writing prompts to group discussions.</string>
    <string name="think_india"><u>Think India</u></string>
    <string name="about_think_india">Think India in cooperation with the MNIT Jaipur seeks to undertake the following activities:

a) Organize interactive group discussions or Sewa activities on campus as well as off campus.

b) Organize debates and talks on issues of national and international importance pertaining to social, economic, developmental concern.

c) To facilitate guests (real life role model) to deliver lectures on issues concerning the society at large.

d) Organize Fellowship/internship programs with various Sewa organizations.

e) Organize flagship Conferences, Workshop and Seminar.

f) To encourage participation of the students and faculty members’ in social cum academic activities which concerns today\'s society.

g) To form a Study Circle to discuss the issues among students and faculties on current topics which affect the society as well as to invite any eminent guest speaker.

h) Adoption of a village near institution to spread awareness through organizing medical camp and adopting tree plantation activity.
</string>
    <string name="nss"><u>NSS</u></string>
    <string name="about_nss">The overall aim of National Service Scheme is to give an extension dimension to the higher education system and orient the student youth to community service while they are studying in educational institution. It is necessary to arouse the social conscience of the students, and to provide them an opportunity to work with the people who are in need of basic necessities of life. This will expose them to the realities of life and bring about a change in their social perception. Various activities can be adult school, coaching for poor and slum students, education of the deprived communities about their rights and the government schemes for their upliftment, distribution of leftover food to the deprived community, creating self-employment for them, encouraging child education, women empowerment, women upliftment etc. NSS volunteers may work for villages and slums and volunteer to complete 12O hours of regular activities during an academic year\'. A village/ slum may be selected for implementation of NSS Programme. Programmes like Blood Donation Camps, Swash Bharat Camps etc may be organised.</string>
    <string name="travel"><u>Travel and heritage visit Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_travel">Many of us wants to be a wanderer with a dream of exploring the whole world ,to discover the hidden gems of nature and to gain knowledge and facts about the marvel ancient architecture. A club with a focus on travel that organises activities such as hiking, cycling tours, trips, and camps, as well as the discovery and documenting of heritage sites in and around Jaipur and the surrounding area.</string>
    <string name="electoral_literacy"><u>Electoral Literacy Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_electoral_literacy">An Electoral Literacy Club is a platform to engage students through interesting activities and hands-on experience to sensitise them on their electoral rights and familiarise them with the electoral process of registration and voting. At ELCs, learning meets fun. Activities and Games are designed to stimulate and motivate students provoking them to think and ask questions. Through ELC, Election Commission of India, aims at strengthening the culture of electoral participation among young and future voters. In the ELCs, members will be part of interesting and thought-provoking activities and games.</string>
    <string name="quiz"><u>Quiz Club</u></string>
    <string name="about_quiz">Enables students to take part in quizzes to evaluate their knowledge in a multitude of areas, including but not limited to science, technology, literature, national and international politics, social science, and more. The goal here is to evaluate the pupils\' level of comprehension on these topics.</string>
    <string name="mav"><u>The Mavericks MNIT</u></string>
    <string name="about_mav">As its motto suggests, "Awareness Overpowers Ignorance," and that is exactly what The Mavericks strive to do: make students more aware of current events happening all around the world. Activities include a TEDx chapter, surveys, webinars, Polls, and Journalism events, as well as Placement presentations highlighting the various academic and professional options that can be taken after graduation.</string>
</resources>