<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="about_dsw">Students are the most integral part of any institution; therefore, it is our top most priority to provide a healthy, safe and sound environment to them here at the campus so that they continue to grow and excel holistically without any hindrance. The force that works tirelessly to accomplish this mission is led by the Office of Student Welfare.</string>
    <string name="_001">1. Registration of the newly admitted UG students in academic session 2022–23.</string>
    <string name="_002">2. Orientation program for fresh entrant students.</string>
    <string name="_003">3. Student Identity Card.</string>
    <string name="_004">4. Coordinating Anti-Ragging activities.</string>
    <string name="_005">5. Coordinating Cultural activities of the students.</string>
    <string name="_006">6. Coordinating Technical Societies at Institute and department level and Funding support for participating in external technical events.</string>
    <string name="_007">7. Coordinating and organizing activities related to MoE Flagship Programmes.</string>
    <string name="_008">8. Preparing Student magazine.</string>
    <string name="_009">9. Unnat Bharat Abhiyan (UBA) program.</string>
    <string name="_010">10. Issuance of Student Insurance and Character Certificate</string>
    <string name="_011">11. Managing all scholarships for UG, PG, and PhD (except institute assistant-ship).</string>
    <string name="_012">12. Maintain Discipline, Wellness and Welfare of Students.</string>
    <string name="_013">13. 13.	 Financial assistance to students, travel grants, and education loans.</string>
    <string name="_014">14. Providing railways concession</string>
    <string name="_015">15. Managing hostel accommodation and messing facilities for students residing in the campus.</string>
    <string name="_016">16. Providing sports facilities for students and staff by organizing indoor and outdoor games and providing fund support for participating in external sports events.</string>

    <string name="about_dsw_text"><u>About DSW</u></string>
    <string name="Key_Tasks_of_Dean_Student_Welfare_Office_text"><u>Key Tasks of Dean Student Welfare Office</u></string>
</resources>